

MIGUEL PINTO

JUNIOR FRONTEND **DEVELOPER**

CONTACT



migueljcpinto@gmail.com



Annette-von-Aretin Str.7 81737 Munich



((,) +49 (0) 172 6740488



LinkedIn



GitHub



<u>Homepage - Portfolio</u>

TECH SKILLS

- JavaScript ES8+
- · React.js
- HTML5
- CSS3
- MongoDB
- Node.js
- Next.js
- Git Workflow
- Figma (Basics)

LANGUAGES

- Portuguese Native
- German working language
- English Good knowledge
- Spanish Good knowledge

HOBBIES

Running, swimming, CrossFit, cinema and travelling

PERSONAL PROFILE

Passionate about healthcare and digital technology, I have advanced my career as a nurse while simultaneously cultivating my interest in web development. With my skills as an analytical, task-oriented problem solver and my experience collaborating in multidisciplinary teams as an ICU nurse, I can make a valuable contribution. I am excited about new opportunities and look forward to creating positive impacts together.

EXPERIENCE

Trainee Web Development

Neuefische I School and Pool for digital talent Intensive Coding-Bootcamp in Part-time - 540 Hours Final project- Team'Up

Health Care and Nursing

Interdisciplinary intensive care unit Clinic rechts der Isar, Munich 2018 - Currently

Stroke Unit/IMC Nursing Clinic rechts der Isar, Munich 2015 - 2018

Neurological nursing - Stroke Unit Nordwest Hospital, Frankfurt am Main 2012 - 2015

EDUCATION

Bootcamp Web Development

Neuefische - March 2023 - September 2023

School and Pool for Digital Talent Part-time intensive coding bootcamp

Wound Expert ICW

Training

Clinic rechts der Isar 2020 - 2021

Special Nursing Stroke-Unit

Training

University Medicine of the Johannes Gutenberg University, Mainz 2014 - 2015

Bachelor of Science in Nursing

Bachelor

Nursing School Coimbra, Portugal 2007 - 2011

